(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-05T23:07:54.099366",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": false,
"max_retries_exceeded": true,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.8-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ローソンへお越しの皆さん！
Hello to everyone visiting Lawson!
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
[Lawson Campaign Confirmed!]
今回はこの6人が登場！
[Featuring these six talents this time!]
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
[Details to be released on Monday, March 9!]
エキスポのバンダイブースを大追跡！
A closer look into the Expo's Bandai booth!
注目の新商品を初公開！
Unveiling hot new products for the first time!
会場限定、スペシャルフォトブース！
Venue exclusive: Special Photo Booth!
限定カードももらえる！
You can also get exclusive cards!
特設サイトも公開中！
The special website is also live!
来場せよ！
Come visit!
今年も
[This year as well...]
JOYSOUND みるハコで配信決定！！
[Streaming confirmed on JOYSOUND Miruhako!!]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Notice: The concert will be starting soon]
ご来場のお客様へ：照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
[For Visitors: Please beware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK]
hololive Dreams 事前登録受付中！
[hololive Dreams: Pre-registration Now Open!]
ホロリス各位！声出してけ～！
Attention Holo-fans! Make some noise~!
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams]
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony, words layered together,
届け
reach out!
Yeah!
うたかたと描いては
Depicting them as transient,
消えっこないと笑ってた
we laughed, knowing they'd never fade.
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
A vision of the future—let's see what follows that day.
手と手繋いで 風も着こなして
Hand in hand, making the wind our own,
扉を叩いて 連れて行くよ
knocking on the door, I'll take you along.
どんなことも きっと 一緒なら 叶えていける
Anything, surely, if we're together, we can make it come true.
La la la la...
鳴り止まない 希望を乗せる
Carrying never-ending hope...
ほら
Look,
La la la...
聴こえてる (聴こえてる)
Can you hear it? (Can you hear it?)
歌
The song...
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
In harmony, our overlapping words
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond the vivid days,
映し出す (響く)
reflecting them (resonating),
彩るよ ストーリー
coloring our story.
ハートに結んだ夢が 空へ駆けていく
The dream tied to our hearts races into the sky,
きらめきに乗せて あなたへ
carried upon the sparkle, to you.
届け メロディー どこまでも
Reach out, melody, reaching endlessly!
何気ないことも思い出す
I remember even the casual moments,
一人じゃないよって深呼吸
taking a deep breath, knowing I'm not alone.
見たい景色楽しむ魔法の言葉
The magic words to enjoy the sights I want to see;
ふと気付いて ふと振り返って また君を知って
suddenly realizing, looking back, and learning more about you,
その度に ちょっと勇気出して 明日へ飛び込んでいけ
each time gathering a little courage to leap into tomorrow!
La la la...
降り積もる 道標はまだ
The piling guideposts are still...
La la la...
覚えてる (覚えてる)
I still remember (I remember)
歌
the song...
ハーモニー 手を伸ばしたら
In harmony, when we reach out our hands,
足跡に 虹がかかる
a rainbow bridges across our footprints.
広がる (響く)
Spreading out (resonating),
つながるステージ
a connected stage.
ハートに記した場所へ 運ぶ約束を
Carrying the promise to the place etched in our hearts,
輝きに乗せて 世界へ
carried upon the brilliance, to the world,
響け メロディー いつまでも
resonate, melody, forevermore!
君と踏み出したあの一歩 あの瞬間が
That first step I took with you, that very moment,
宝物だって胸を張る 今は
I can proudly say is my treasure now.
泣き顔 笑顔に変えていくから
Because I'll keep turning tears into smiles,
色褪せないまま
never fading away.
混ざり合う僕らの声 ほら
Our mingling voices, look,
聴こえてる (聴こえてる)
can you hear it? (Can you hear it?)
歌
The song...
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
In harmony, our overlapping words
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond the vivid days,
映し出す (響く)
reflecting them (resonating),
彩るよ ストーリー
coloring our story.
ハートに結んだ夢が 空へ駆けていく
The dream tied to our hearts races into the sky,
きらめきに乗せて あなたへ
carried upon the sparkle, to you,
世界へ (響け)
to the world (resonate),
愛を (届け)
our love (reach out),
メロディー どこまでも
melody, reaching endlessly!
パレ・パレ・パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
呼び合う声を合図に
With our calling voices as the signal,
パレ・パレ・パレ 探しに行く
parade, parade, parade, we're off to search!
スタートはワンダーランド
Starting from Wonderland!
色鳥の綴った
With the song woven by colorful birds
歌が始まりだって走った
as our beginning, we began to run.
遠く暗闇に灯った
Lit up far away in the darkness,
それは眩しすぎた名前
it was a name that shone too brightly,
それは優しすぎる思い出
it was memories that were all too gentle.
もっと近づけと手を伸ばした
Reaching out a hand to get closer,
思いがけず結びあった
we unexpectedly bonded together.
ほら今 迷い子はこんなになった
Look now, the lost children have grown like this!
パレ・パレ・パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along both the frustration and the love!
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りばかり...
With nothing but humble prayers...
...な兆し
...a sure sign,
君を見つけたこと
finding you,
胸を張れるよう
so I can hold my head high,
ここから これから
from here, from now on,
Our Bright Parade
頼りない予感を歌おう
Let's sing of this uncertain premonition,
恥ずかしくなんてないよ
there's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けないイマジナリー
An imaginary world no one can unravel,
いつかまた会えるおまじない
a spell to meet again someday.
あの日 ゼロに始まったストーリー
The story that started from zero that day.
数え切れない言の葉
Countless words,
数えるような想いじゃないさ
these feelings aren't something to be counted.
ほら 今 僕らを
Look, right now,
一つと呼ぼう
let's call ourselves one!
パレ パレ パレ
Parade, parade, parade,
慈しむんだよ
cherish it.
許し合える刹那
In this fleeting moment of mutual forgiveness,
夜はきらめく
the night sparkles.
雨 晴れ 枯れ
Rain, shine, or wither,
待ったことない空
under a sky that never waits,
繰り返した日々とは
all the days we went through...
君とあることさ
mean being with you.
君とあることなんだ
They truly mean being with you!
「ただいま」を聞けば
Whenever we hear "I'm home,"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
we'll shout back, "Welcome home!"
当たり前じゃないから
Because none of this is taken for granted.
パレ パレ パレ
Parade, parade, parade,
輝くんだよ
we're going to shine!
暗がりを満たすのは
The ones who fill the darkness,
君と僕だ
are you and me.
パレ パレ パレ
Parade, parade, parade,
輝くんだよ
we're going to shine!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れて
Taking both our frustration and our love along,
愛で 風 夢 羽
with love, wind, dreams, and wings,
飛び立てるさ
we can soar high!
ささやかな祈りばかり
Just modest little prayers,
終わりなき兆し
an endless sign,
君と飛び込んでゆく
diving right in together with you,
素敵なスタートさ
it's a wonderful start.
ここから これから
From here, from now on,
Our Bright Parade
フェスフェス！ ステージ1、盛り上がっていきましょー！
Fes, fes! Stage 1, let's get hyped up!
ステージ1、最初から飛ばしていくぞー！
Stage 1, we're going full throttle right from the start!
It's on, turn round and leave
タコメーター ゾロ目で ゾロ目で 揃った時 見えた勝負
When matching digits lined up on the tachometer, I saw the showdown!
焦がして say out 口噛ませ fake
Burn it and say out, gag the fake,
朝飯前 必勝
a piece of cake, a guaranteed win,
豪傑ラッキー トラブル熱狂
heroic luck, wild fervor for trouble!
Tell 'em I win ここらで一丁 展開見せよう
Tell 'em I win, right here, let's show them a twist!
Break a bound, get the dough That's how body fits a flow
Tell 'em I win 振り返しゃ飛び切り 調子も絶好調
Tell 'em I win, looking back it's exceptional, in top form and feeling great!
見せてあげよう 完膚無きまでの勝利法
I'll show you an absolute, flawless way to win!
一つ アイツ 打ち破る勝敗
Overcoming that rival one by one, victory and defeat,
この世界中を手玉にとるまで
until I hold this entire world in the palm of my hand!
Draw in the knife, not for mission, call this heist
Take my soul 奪った対価
take my soul, the price for what was stolen!
You know I catch ya, now everybody bounce
Panic, see my eye, what's a magic show
少年万延 疑惑乱 鉄板のメジャー
Confusion runs wild, an ironclad major!
ハイローリン going money 窮地で踊り狂ったのは誰
High rolling, going money, who was it dancing madly in a pinch?
Check my, check my, check my voice
I said I take it home
You're lucky, I think I'm gonna get, get out
You're lucky, I think I'm gonna get out
Take a breakdown ハイスピードチェイス 安泰なんて笑止
Take a breakdown, high-speed chase, safety is laughable!
Can't catch me かっ飛ばしてけハイウェイ 轟く my name
Can't catch me, blast down the highway, my name roars out!
I'm awake and prominent figures are on the map
誰も邪魔しねぇ 手中に落とすわ
No one can stop me, I'll take it right into my hands!
世の奇怪なカラクリ露わに
Laying bare the world's bizarre mechanisms,
滾るハイを求め 遊び尽...
chasing a boiling high, playing it out to...
Hold into time, put everything on the line
Hold onto time, put everything on the line
So you're coming in a bind
That's when I getcha!
Now everybody panics, cinematic, it's what's so amazing
安全圏じゃもういられない 止まんないわ
Can't stay in the safe zone anymore, can't stop won't stop
Yeah, let's come at a dramatic
Yeah, let's make it dramatic
そう 一口味わったなら最後
Right, once you get a single taste, it's over
Show time! It's show time!
Child's play, I take it home
Child's play, I'll take it home
勝者の行く末 待つは滅びか
The victor's fate—does ruin await?
勝負の行方は神のみぞ知る
The outcome of the battle, only God knows
Like the drum and the brass in the song
Like the drums and brass in the song
This game is only just begun
This game has only just begun
Get lucky, I think I'm gonna get, get out
Get lucky, I think I'm gonna...
溢れる欲望 導くままに 溺れず君臨するあたし
Guided by overflowing desires, I reign supreme without drowning
Suc-suc-success I embody, it's a hobby
Way I make everybody yell
The way I make everybody yell
Close call, it's all clear
Can't touch me, I can't hear you
Hello, we going money
Hello, we're going for the money
狂気で踊り狂う この鼓動
Dancing wildly in madness, this heartbeat
Show time! It's show time!
Catch up! I'm a get-get done
Catch up! I'm gonna get it done
Star-star crowd
Slash show and early, I'm getting lucky tonight
I'm a get-get done
I'm gonna get it done
Watch your back
思うままに理想を描いたような
Painting ideals just as I imagined,
勝利を持って take it home
I'll take victory home
幕張ー！
Makuhariー!
一生タイム 一緒にいたいよ
Lifetime Showtime, I want to be with you forever
Lifetime showtime anytime BAU BAU yeah!
二人は ハッピーラッキー パピーシスターズ
We're the Happy Lucky Puppy Sisters!
もっとこっち来てー！
Come closer to us!
フワ！モコ！フワ！モコ！
Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
BAU! BAU! BAU BAU BAU!
心も身体もフワフワで
Both heart and body feel so fluffy and light,
気持ちごと浮くことあるけど
and our spirits might float away sometimes,
吠えれば魔界の番犬で
but when we bark, we're the Demon Realm guard dogs,
あなたの笑顔を守りたいよ
and we want to protect your smile!
フワ！モコ！フワ！モコ！
Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco!
いたずら大好きペロペロモコ
Moco loves mischief and licking around,
お散歩大好きリードはいらぬ
loves going for walks, no leash needed!
どこでもモココついていくから
Mococo will follow you anywhere,
フワモコたちも連れて行って
so take FUWAMOCO along with you!
二人で吠える
Together, we'll bark!
一生タイム 一緒にいたいよ
Lifetime Showtime, I want to be with you forever
Lifetime showtime anytime BAU BAU yeah!
Show guys, sing with you
Dazzling, sparkling, forever glow
一生タイム 一緒にいたいよ
Lifetime Showtime, I want to be with you forever
Lifetime showtime anytime BAU BAU yeah!
二人は ハッピーラッキー パピーシスターズ
We're the Happy Lucky Puppy Sisters!
BAU!
昔々檻の中で ワクワク ドキドキ 抑えられ...
Once upon a time in a cage, excitement and thrills barely contained...
BAU!
爆走鬼ごっこになっちゃって
Turned into a high-speed game of tag,
大脱走 It's play time!
a great escape! It's playtime!
ゴールを目指せ 足は止まらない
Aim for the goal, our feet won't stop!
笑顔一番 拍手も止まらない
Smiles come first, the applause won't stop either!
今はまだまだ怖がりだけど
We're still scaredy-cats right now, but...
二人の絆は強いから
because the bond between the two of us is strong,
絶対壊せない
it can never be broken!
だから いつだって いつだって
So whenever, always...
Lifetime showtime
BAU BAU!
一生涯 walk with you
For a lifetime, walk with you
Good time, bad time, it doesn't matter
Good times, bad times, it doesn't matter
いつだって いつだって
Whenever, always...
Lifetime showtime everyday BAU BAU yeah!
二人は ハッピーラッキー パピーシスターズ
We're the Happy Lucky Puppy Sisters!
Let's together!
All together!
フワモコ BAU BAU everybody モフモフ
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU, everybody mofumofu!
Hello Hello BAU BAU everybody モフモフ
Hello Hello BAU BAU, everybody mofumofu!
ダメダメ NO NO Don't touch the ears
No-no NO NO, don't touch the ears!
モフモフ NO NO Don't touch the tail
Mofumofu NO NO, don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ フワワだよ BAU!
Not a chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa! BAU!
猫じゃないよ モココだよ BAU!
Not a cat, I'm Mococo! BAU!
魔界の番犬シスターズ BAU!
Demon Realm guard dog sisters! BAU!
And together with フワモコ！
And together with FUWAMOCO!
二人の夢を掛け合わせたら
When our dreams multiply together,
目が覚めてしまうほどの 無限大になっちゃう
they expand to an eye-opening infinity!
たくさんあって 叶えきれないかもだけど
There are so many, we might not grant them all, but...
ずっとチャレンジできる 一緒だから
we can keep taking on the challenge, because we're together!
一生タイム 一緒にいたい
Lifetime Showtime, I want to be with you
一生タイム 一緒にいたいよ
Lifetime Showtime, I want to be with you forever
ふわふわモコモコ包まれて
Wrapped in fluffy and soft warmth,
君の笑顔は守りたい 一番の願い
I want to protect your smile, that's my number one wish!
一生タイム 一緒にいたいよ
Lifetime Showtime, I want to be with you forever
Lifetime showtime anytime BAU BAU
一生涯 sing with you
For a lifetime, sing with you
Dazzling, sparkling, forever glow 一生タイム
Dazzling, sparkling, forever glow, Lifetime Showtime
Show me that, your Lifetime Showtime anytime, Bow-Wow-Aaah!
Together we're Ruffianとひとつさ！
Together we're one with the Ruffians!
ラストだよー！
This is the last part!
フワモコ！フワモコ！Bau Bau!
FUWAMOCO! FUWAMOCO! Bau Bau!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
フワモコ！フワモコ！フワモコ！Bau Bau! フワモコ！Bau Bau!
FUWAMOCO! FUWAMOCO! FUWAMOCO! Bau Bau! FUWAMOCO! Bau Bau!
Bau!
誰が何と言おうと、
No matter what anyone says,
今日は クリスマス！
today is Christmas!
これは、
This is...
君との約束の物語...
the story of our promise...
ぺこチキン、いかがでしょうかー！？
How about some Peko Chicken?!
ジューシー バリバリ ジューシー バリバリ
Juicy, crispy! Juicy, crispy!
いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さあさ 今日も元気に 焼いて 焼いて 焼いちゃって
Come on, grilling energetically today, grill, grill, grill it up!
お父様 お母様 お一人様で パーティ様
Fathers, mothers, solo diners, and party guests,
どうでしょう ひとつ ぺこチキン
how about a piece of Peko Chicken?
ええ塩梅さ 焼き上げの
It's grilled to absolute perfection,
あっという間に 行列だ
in the blink of an eye, there's a huge line!
レジへ向かう お腹ぺコンチュ
Heading to the register, hungry Pekonchu,
待たせて Sorry
sorry to keep you waiting!
てんやわんや しちゃうけど
It gets hectic and chaotic,
キッチリ 骨まで 仕上げるぞ
but we'll cook it thoroughly, right to the bone!
ほとばしる 秘伝のスパイス
Bursting with our secret spices,
LOVE & PEACE
美味しくなれだね 唱えて
chant "become delicious"!
じっくり じっくり こんがり こんがり
Slowly, slowly, nicely browned and toasted,
ギラギラと 輝いて
sparkling brightly,
ホッカホカ シャキーン！
piping hot, shakiin!
P・E・K・O・C・H・I・K・I・N
P-E-K-O-C-H-I-K-I-N!
お待たせ ぺこ！
Thanks for waiting, peko!
食らえ！
Eat up!
やめらんねえよ やめらんねえよ ぺこチキン
Can't stop, won't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねえよ とんでもねえよ ぺこチキン
It's unbelievable, mind-blowing, Peko Chicken!
カリッと ジュワッと ホロッと たっぷり アツアツ
Crunchy, juicy, falling off the bone, plenty piping hot!
ほら おひとつ どうでしょう？
Come on, how about a piece?
やめらんねえな やめらんねえな ぺこチキン
You really can't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねえな とんでもねえな ぺこチキン
Truly unbelievable, Peko Chicken!
丸縛り 特ラードに眠る ペロリ おかしくなっちゃう 美味しさ
Trussed and resting in special lard, eat it all up, deliciousness that drives you crazy!
胃腸 温度計！
Stomach thermometer!
全体 温度計！
Whole body thermometer!
チキあっ チキあっ チキあっ チキあっ
Chiki-ah, chiki-ah, chiki-ah, chiki-ah!
お待たせ ぺこ！
Thanks for waiting, peko!
冷めたら チンして ぺこチキン
If it gets cold, just microwave it, Peko Chicken!
あー、あー、この度は ご来店いただき、誠に、誠に ありがとうございます。
Ah, ah... Thank you so, so much for visiting our shop today.
本日も元気に焼けておりますのは、肉汁、脳汁 たっぷり、ぺこチキンでございます。
Grilling up energetically today as well, packed with meat juice and brain juice, is Peko Chicken.
熱く こんがり 冷まさないを モットーに、ジューシー バリバリ、ジューシー バリバリ 取り揃えております。
With the motto "hot, nicely browned, never cold," we have plenty of juicy, crispy chicken in stock.
皆様の日頃のご愛顧に感謝を込めて、ただいまより、チキンフィーバータイム突入とさせていただきます。
In gratitude for everyone's continued patronage, we will now enter Chicken Fever Time!
それでは、お呼び出しを申し上げます。
Now then, we will begin calling your orders!
揚げたてチキンのお客様ー！
Order for freshly fried chicken!
お一人ぼっちのお客様ー！
Order for all the lonely solo customers!
自称パリピのお客様ー！
Order for self-proclaimed party animals!
骨無しチキンのお客様ー！
Order for boneless chicken!
毎日ロックンロールご希望のお客様ー！
Order for customers wanting rock 'n roll every day!
肉汁 脂 マシマシ辛めのお客様ー！
Order with extra meat juice, extra fat, and extra spicy!
限界突破 かぶりつき希望のお客様ー！
Order for customers wanting to break limits and dig right in!
お腹ペコペコのお客様ー！
Order for starving customers!
聖なる夜にはー！
On this holy night...!
チキあっ チキあっ チキあっ チキあっ
Chiki-ah, chiki-ah, chiki-ah, chiki-ah!
黙って頬張るよ ぺこチキン
Just shut up and stuff your cheeks with Peko Chicken!
遅くなってごめんね
Sorry for being late...
やっと言えた世界で
In a world where I can finally say it,
冷えた孤独を温めてあげる
I'll warm up your chilled loneliness.
一人じゃないよ
You're not alone.
冷めた食卓に彩りを
Bringing color to a cold dining table,
これが聖なるぺこチキン
this is the sacred Peko Chicken!
だから！
So!
だからー！
So...!
やめらんねえよ やめらんねえよ ぺこチキン
Can't stop, won't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねえよ とんでもねえよ ぺこチキン
It's unbelievable, mind-blowing, Peko Chicken!
カリッと ジュワッと ホロッと たっぷり アツアツ
Crunchy, juicy, falling off the bone, plenty piping hot!
ほら もうひとつ どうでしょう？
Come on, how about another piece?
冷めてる夜も 冷めてる夜も ぺこチキン
Even on cold nights, cold nights, Peko Chicken!
温めるだけ あっためるだけ ぺこチキン
Just heat it up, just warm it up, Peko Chicken!
丸縛り 特ラードに眠る ペロリ おかしくなっちゃう 美味しさ
Trussed and resting in special lard, eat it all up, deliciousness that drives you crazy!
めっちゃ 温度計！
Super thermometer!
すっごい 温度計！
Incredible thermometer!
チキあっ チキあっ チキあっ チキあっ
Chiki-ah, chiki-ah, chiki-ah, chiki-ah!
お待たせ ぺこ！
Thanks for waiting, peko!
今夜は 一緒に ぺこチキン
Tonight, let's have Peko Chicken together!
ジューシー バリバリ ジューシー バリバリ
Juicy, crispy! Juicy, crispy!
いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さあさ 今日も元気に 焼いて 焼いて 焼いちゃって
Come on, grilling energetically today, grill, grill, grill it up!
お父様 お母様 お一人様で パーティ様
Fathers, mothers, solo diners, and party guests,
どうでしょう ひとつ ぺこチキン！
how about a piece of Peko Chicken!
Error processing subtitles for this segment.
この場を借りて...
Taking this opportunity...
ま、良ければさ、みんなソロ曲の時に...
Well, if you don't mind, during each of our solo songs...
ファンの皆に何してほしいかっていうのちょっと...
...what we'd like the fans to do...
ああー！わぁ！
Ah! Wow!
ふーちゃんありますか？サイリウムの色、ペンライトの色、何色がいいとかさ。
Fu-chan, do you have one? Like what glowstick or penlight color you'd prefer?
ふふ、これはオレンジだろ！
Haha, for this, it's gotta be orange!
え、オレンジ？！え、嘘ぉ！
Eh, orange?! No way!
え、でも、なんか... / 違うのか
Wait, but... / Is it not?
曲に合わせて...
Along to the song...
曲に合わせて、こう手拍子があったら...
If there could be hand claps along to the song...
クラップとか、あとはなんかエモい感じにしてもらったりとかしてほしいなぁ
like rhythmic claps, and getting into an emotional vibe, that's what I'd love!
おお、いいですね！
Ooh! That sounds great!
なるほどね！ほうほうほう。
I see! Uh-huh, uh-huh.
わためは？
How about you, Watame?
えっ、やっぱ一番でっかい声を...
Well, I definitely want your loudest voices...
出してほしいなと思ったり... / でっかい声！
to come shouting out! / Loud voices!
でっかい声！でっかい声出せるよなー？！
Loud voices! You guys can make some loud noise, right?!
でっかい声ー！
Loud voices!
出せるよなー？！
Can you do it?!
じゃあわためのソロ曲の時もよろしくお願いします！そしてポルカはどうですか？
Then please give it your all for Watame's solo song too! And how about you, Polka?
もちろん盛り上がってくれるよなー？！おー？！
Naturally you're gonna get hyped up, right?! Oh yeah?!
おーー！
Yeahhh!
ポルカの時はよろしくお願いします！
Please show me some love during my turn!
そしてですね、白上ちょっとペンラに触れたんですけど、白上のソロ曲の時はぜひとも皆さん、あの...
And also, I briefly mentioned penlights earlier, but during my solo song, everyone...
白上のカラーではなく、皆さんの最推しのカラーでお願いします！
please shine your absolute favorite member's color, not mine!
ええーー！？
Ehhhh?!
優しい！優しい！
That's so sweet!
もちろん、でもすこん部の方はね、白とか青でもいいですけども！
Of course, Sukon-bu can use white or blue too, though!
青でもいいですけども！今回のね、Day 1含めホロライブプロダクションに好きな推しのカラーが皆さんあると思います。
Blue is fine too! But everyone has their own favorite member's color across Hololive Production, including Day 1.
白上のソロ曲の時はぜひとも、皆さんの最推しのカラーで...
So during my solo song, please wave the color of your number one favorite...
振ってくれると、多分すーっごい良い景色になるんじゃないかと思ってます！
and I think it will create a truly spectacular view!
それでは白上のソロ曲もお願いしまーす！
So please cheer for my solo song as well!
お願いしまーす！
Please support her!
さあ！じゃあ配信のみんなが見てる、なんかあの羨ましい感じに...
All right! Now, to make all the viewers watching the stream feel envious...
みんな「イエーイ！」ってさ、言ったり言ったり配信の皆に...
let's all shout "Yeah!" to the viewers on the stream...
イエーイ！！
Yeahhh!!
このあとも盛り上がっていくぜー！ / イエーイ！
Let's keep this excitement going! / Yeah!
さあ、では続いての楽曲も準備できてるっぽいのでね、メンバーが！
Now then, it looks like the members are ready for the next song!
できたー！
We're ready!
行きますか、じゃあ！ / はい！
Shall we get started, then? / Yes!
今回皆さん、『Ridin' on Dreams』がテーマなので！
Everyone, since this event's theme is "Ridin' on Dreams"...
これで締めたいと思います！いきますよー？ / はーい！
we'd like to close with that! Ready, everyone? / Ready!
せーの！
Ready, set...
Ridin' on Dreams!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended! Thank you for watching!